Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Miniatures, Props, and Pieces, 1980-1993 and undated, (27 boxes)
  - Citadel
    - Dark Ages, 6 packs., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Dark Ages, 6 packs., D04403952R (Box P8)
    - Dragon, 2 packs., D04403971S (Box P27)
    - Dungeons and Dragons, 1 pack., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Dungeons and Dragons, 1 pack., D04403948W (Box P4)
    - Dwarven Stonecut, 2 packs., D04403971S (Box P27)
    - Elf, 2 packs., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Eternal Champion, 1 pack., D04403948W (Box P4)
    - Eternal Champion, 2 packs., D04405780S (Box P30)
    - Fantasy Adventures, 1 pack., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Fighter, 12 packs., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Great Imperial Dragon, 1 pack., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - Lord of the Rings, 1 pack., D04403948W (Box P4)
    - Lord of the Rings, 1 pack., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Monsters, 2 packs., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Realm of Chaos, 1 pack., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Talisman, 4 packs., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Townsfolk and Villagers, 1 pack., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Undead, 2 packs., D04403947V (Box P3)
    - Undead, 11 packs., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Warrior, 1 pack., D04403947V (Box P3)
  - Dark Horse
    - Elementals, 2 packs., D04403953S (Box P9)
    - Groo, 2 packs., D04403953S (Box P9)
  - Dragon Tooth
    - Dragon Tooth, 15 packs., D04403962S (Box P18)
  - FASA Corporation
    - BattleTech, 2 packs., D04403946U (Box P2)
    - BattleTech, 5 patches., D04405779- (Box P29)
    - Star Trek, 1 map., D04405779- (Box P29)
  - Garrison
    - Greenwood and Ball, 1 pack., D04403950P (Box P6)
  - GDW
    - Space 1889, 4 packs., D04405782U (Box P32)
  - Grenadier Models
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 3 packs., D04403954T (Box P10)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 7 packs., D04403968Y (Box P24)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 2 packs., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Colossal Lords, 1 pack., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Cthulhu, 17 packs., D04403954T (Box P10)
    - Cthulhu, 2 packs., D04403968Y (Box P24)
    - Dragon Lords, 15 packs., D04403955U (Box P11)
    - Dragon Lords, 19 packs., D04403958X (Box P14)
    - Dragon Lords, 7 packs., D04403960Q (Box P16)
    - Dragon Lords, 5 packs., D04403968Y (Box P24)
    - Dragon Lords, 3 packs., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Dragons, 1 pack., D04403960Q (Box P16)
    - Dungeon Floors, 1 pack., D04403960Q (Box P16)
    - Fantasy Lords, 2 packs., D04403949X (Box P5)
    - Fantasy Lords, 8 packs., D04403954T (Box P10)
    - Fantasy Lords, 6 packs., D04403968Y (Box P24)
    - Fantasy Lords, 9 packs., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Fantasy Personalities, 6 packs., D04403954T (Box P10)
    - Fantasy Personalities, 6 packs., D04403968Y (Box P24)
    - Fantasy Personalities, 2 packs., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Fantasy Warriors, 2 packs., D04403954T (Box P10)
    - Heroes, 5 packs., D04403949X (Box P5)
    - Lord of the Rings, 1 pack., D04403968Y (Box P24)
    - Lord of the Rings, 1 pack., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Masterpiece Editions, 1 pack., D04403968Y (Box P24)
    - Shadow Run, 2 packs., D04403954T (Box P10)
    - Shadow Run, 1 pack., D04403960Q (Box P16)
    - Special Edition, 1 pack., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Traveller, 3 packs., D04403968Y (Box P24)
    - Western Gunfighter, 1 pack., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Wizzards and Warriors, 3 packs., D04403960Q (Box P16)
    - Wizzards and Warriors, 1 pack., D04403968Y (Box P24)
  - Heritage
    - Champions, 5 packs., D04403957W (Box P13)
    - Conan, 11 packs., D04643790X (Box P41)
    - Dragons, 5 packs., D04403957W (Box P13)
    - Dungeon Dwellers, 8 packs., D04403957W (Box P13)
    - Fantastiques, 1 pack., D04403957W (Box P13)
    - The Great Dragon, 1 pack., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - John Carter, Warlord of Mars, 4 packs., D04643790X (Box P41)
    - Knights and Magick, 4 packs., D04403957W (Box P13)
  - Judges Guild
    - Character Chronicle cards, 1 pack., D04405779- (Box P29)
    - Dungeon Tac cards, 1 pack., D04405779- (Box P29)
  - Martian Metals
    - Dragon Slayers, 11 pack., D04403967X (Box P23)
    - RuneQuest, 3 packs., D04403967X (Box P23)
    - Traveller, 12 packs., D04403967X (Box P23)
    - Traveller, 9 packs., D04405781T (Box P31)
    - Worlds of Fantasy, 1 pack., D04403967X (Box P23)
  - Masterpiece Miniatures
    - Masterpiece Miniatures, 5 packs., D04403950P (Box P6)
  - MetalMagic Miniatures
    - Asterix, 3 packs., D04403945T (Box P1)
  - Miniature Figurines
    - The Sword and the Flame, 4 packs., D04403959Y (Box P15)
    - Valley of the Four Winds, 7 packs., D04403959Y (Box P15)
  - Pinnacle Products
    - Dinosaurs, 1 pack., D04403945T (Box P1)
    - Fantasy Lords, 1 pack., D04403945T (Box P1)
  - RAFM Fantasy
    - Fantasy Miniatures, 9 packs., D04403951Q (Box P7)
    - Traveller: New Era, 8 packs., D04403951Q (Box P7)
  - Ral Partha
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 41 packs., D04403966W (Box P22)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 65 packs., D04405783V (Box P33)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 4 packs., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons: Dragon Lance, 3 packs., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons: Forgotten Realms, 2 packs., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - All Things Dark and Dangerous, 19 packs., D04403970R (Box P26)
    - All Things Dark and Dangerous, 4 packs., D04405780S (Box P30)
    - All Things Dark and Dangerous, 1 pack., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - BattleTech, 2 packs., D04403965V (Box P21)
    - Chaos Wars, 2 packs., D04403965V (Box P21)
    - Children of the Night, 5 packs., D04403964U (Box P20)
    - Colonials, 5 packs., D04403970R (Box P26)
    - Dragonscale, 1 pack., D04403970R (Box P26)
    - Elf Quest, 6 packs., D04403961R (Box P17)
    - Great Dragon, 1 pack., D04403965V (Box P21)
    - Imports, 26 packs., D04403964U (Box P20)
    - Imports, 1 pack., D04403965V (Box P21)
    - Imports, 8 packs., D04405782U (Box P32)
    - Imports, 6 packs., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - Personalities, 14 packs., D04403963T (Box P19)
    - Personalities, 2 packs., D04405780S (Box P30)
    - Personalities, 3 packs., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - Ral Partha, 2 packs., D04403970R (Box P26)
    - RuneQuest, 3 packs., D04403965V (Box P21)
    - Shadow Run, 3 packs., D04405780S (Box P30)
    - The Adventurers, 13 packs., D04403969Z (Box P25)
    - Three-Stage Characters, 2 packs., D04403970R (Box P26)
  - Reaper Miniatures
    - Dark Heaven, 1 pack., D04403950P (Box P6)
  - Steve Jackson Games
    - Cardboard Heroes, 3 packs., D04403945T (Box P1)
    - Cardboard Heroes, 13 packs., D04405779- (Box P29)
    - Cardboard Heroes, 3 packs., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Car Wars, 2 expansion sets., D04405779- (Box P29)
  - Superior Models
    - Wizards and Lizards, 1 pack., D04403950P (Box P6)
  - Tabletop Miniatures
    - Laserburn, 2 packs., D04403950P (Box P6)
  - TAG Industry
    - Children of Fantasy, 1 pack., D04564080R (Box P34)
    - Children of the Nile, 10 packs., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - Children of Valhalla, 2 packs., D04564081S (Box P35)
    - TAG Industry, 2 packs., D04403953S (Box P9)
  - Task Force Games
    - Swordplay!, 4 packs., D04403953S (Box P9)
  - TSR
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 8 packs., D04403956V (Box P12)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 12 packs., D04405781T (Box P31)
    - Classics, 2 packs., D04403956V (Box P12)
    - DragonLance, 1 trail map., D04405779- (Box P29)
    - Fantasy Figures, 1 pack., D04403956V (Box P12)
    - Indiana Jones, 1 pack., D04403956V (Box P12)
    - Marvel Superheroes, 3 packs., D04403956V (Box P12)
  - Miscellaneous Game Aids
    - Various game aids, D04403986Y (Box P28)
      Game accessories provided by companies like TSR and Judges Guild to accompany RPGs. Aids vary from 3D pop up tiles to system maps.
- Manuscripts, undated, (2 boxes)
  Campaign notes and records kept by the Murrays for a variety of games.
  - Gameplay notes
    - Blank sheets, D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - 2300 A.D. (Box MS1)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons - Dungeon Masters Adventure Logs, D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons - Miscellaneous, D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - Call of Cthulhu, D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - Dark Conspiracy, D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - Edwin's Dungeon, D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - Terry's Dungeon (2 folders), D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - Notes for Dungeons and Dragons, D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - Megatraveller, D02340923N (Box MS1)
    - Space 1889, D02340923N (Box MS1)
  - Character notecards, unlabeled, D04405794X (Box MS2)